Once someone opens the door, follow whatever directions they give you.
It was a lot of fun. Now good luck to you.
Yeah, thanks.
Hey, does someone named Mihail live here?
Go do some shopping at Deke Sakura by the station.
Use this card at the checkout.
Very good, sir. Please follow me this way.
Thank you.
There's a lot more people than last year.
Wonder if there's anybody I know.
Hey!
You walked all over us last year.
But it's gonna be a lot different this time.
We all put ourselves through some intense training after what happened.
Now our team works perfect, so good luck trying to...
Thanks for coming, everyone.
This year, 1,489 applicants have made it this far.
But the examiner for the second phase asked me to trim that number down to about 300.
But as for the exam itself, lunch is two hours away.
So knock out five people before then.
Once all five are down, grab their badges and come see me.
I'll be right on the other side of the door.
All right.
As soon as it closes, that's your cue to get started.
Every face of the exam should be like this.
A hunter's gotta be strong, and this helps find and weed out the weaklings.
You're here too, old man.
Sucks for you.
I'll pass this year.
And just me.
He's totally out of our league.
That kid was born to be a top-rate hunter.
This will be our last year trying out for the hunter exam.
Took you long enough.
It's already been a full hour and a half.
What are the others doing?
They're all asleep.
Huh?
It just took me a little while to collect all the badges.
What now?
Second phase?
That won't be necessary, I'm afraid.
He's already demonstrated his skill quite sufficiently.
Killua, inhabitant of the shadows.
He's certainly matured since we saw him last.
Applicant 1219, Killua.
Here.
Congratulations.
You passed.
Welcome back, Killua.
How was it?
Well, I aced it in no time, naturally.
Yeah!
I'm sorry to interrupt your celebration, but take a look at these spell cards.
Wow.
There's even an S-rank card.
So how much do you think we can sell it for?
I'm not sure, but why don't we go and ask around?
No.
We should use it wisely.
So what do you think, Killua?
I guess it's safe to hold onto it.
It's not going to get stolen with all these defensive spells.
Have you guys tried any of these out yet?
Just the blackout curtain one.
Why only one?
Why even have them if you don't use them?
Here.
Start off by using this one.
It lets you choose any player you've met and have a talk with them.
Who should we talk to?
First, let's look at who's available.
Alright, contact on!
I didn't know there'd be so many.
Hey, when'd you run into him?
Huh?
Chrollo!
Hold on, who's Chrollo?
I haven't seen him.
Well, not inside of the game anyway.
Does that mean you passed each other without noticing?
What are you two talking about?
But I don't get it.
I could have sworn Kurapika sealed his nen, didn't he?
He sure did.
And you have to use nen just to get inside the game.
Who is this Kurapika?
If that's the case, then that means...
Come on!
What the hell are you guys talking about?
Oh, I get it now.
That's what's going on.
It isn't funny.
Just explain to us what's happening.
Sorry about that.
This probably isn't the boss.
He hasn't exorcised the nen from his body.
Exorcism?
It's quite possible.
It is?
Of course.
If you're able to place nen on others, there would have to be a way to remove it as well.
So does that mean that Chrollo removed Kurapika's nen and then entered the game?
Why would he come here?
I've got no idea, but we should probably let Kurapika know.
In that case, I'm going to hop out of the game again.
Why don't you use a spell card to leave?
Hold on to it.
I'll be back in four hours.
I should have realized it sooner.
Fact is, this island is due east of York New City.
Straight shot.
Perhaps to the east one can be tracked.
The one most needed you're sure to find.
I see.
The boss came to find someone to exorcise that nen.
He probably arrived here the same way we did, but then Razor kicked him out.
I assume that's when he realized this was Greed Island.
But now that the boss can't use nen anymore, he can't enter through the usual channels.
So he must have hired someone to come to the island for him.
And he had them use his name as a hidden message for the rest of us.
The exorcist is on Greed Island.
Another change in plans, huh?
Let's bring everybody else out here.
I agree.
Then all of us will look for the exorcist.
One small correction.
Huh?
It's you.
Hisoka!
See, using Chrollo's name was actually my idea.
But I didn't know that entering any name you like was an option.
Or at least not until I had already gotten inside.
You should be praising my initiative.
If not for me, you never would have understood Chrollo's message.
So that's what this is all about, huh?
I've got half a mind to kill you right here and now.
But I'll leave that to the boss.
Well, if I can help further use contact to find me.
And I'll let you know if I happen to learn anything new.
So long.
I didn't think the boss would have hired Hisoka.
Guess he didn't have much of a choice, but still.
I'm betting that he offered him a duel, post-exorcism.
Probably.
But now it's only a matter of time until the boss comes back.
I doubt it.
If he or one of the other spiders were to attempt to remove my Nen, I would know about it immediately.
There's no other way around it.
So when you set up your ability, you took something like this into account?
Of course I did.
If you're able to place Nen on others.
It stands to reason that the ability to remove it exists as well.
It's common sense.
Well, just thought I'd let you know.
You can do whatever you want with it.
I appreciate that.
You have my gratitude.
Did you need anything?
What am I supposed to do?
What will I do this month?
Please, tell me.
What should I do now?
It's going to be alright.
Just let me handle it.
What do you know about it?
What the hell good are you if you have no idea what's going to happen in the future?
Nihon, I need her.
Restore her at once.
Damn it.
How could this have happened?
I wonder what's wrong.
Why did it stop coming out all of a sudden?
See ya!
Well, it looks like it's not the real Prolulu Silver.
Wait, it's not?
Talk to Kurapika.
He was pretty calm about it.
By the way he responded, he didn't sound concerned.
It sounds like you got all worked up over nothing.
Now if you ask me, you should get back to focusing on yourselves.
Us!
Start with the basics.
We're not going to train.
We've gotten distracted.
But it's time we start trying to beat this game.
It's said that the legendary King White Stag Beetle lives only in this tree.
And that there's only one way to capture it.
Hit the tree and shake it out.
Show me rock!
John can't rock!
Oh wow!
It's raining bugs everywhere!
Found it!
Difficulty reg A.
Oh right!
That makes three King White Stag Beetle cards!
You know, you could have gotten more if you'd just thrown a real punch.
Yeah, you're probably right.
But I didn't want to damage the tree.
There is no such girl here in this mansion.
And even if there were, you would never be able to find her.
Not with all the traps that you would have to get past first.
Found her!
She was hidden in a room deep underground.
What?
Damn you!
A gold dust girl.
Rank A!
But the guard was only an F rank.
Next, let's head to Darius, the gambling town.
Oh man, the Antokiba contest.
That's supposed to be today, right?
We're passing through, so let's give it a try.
The winner this month is Team Killua and Gon!
A paladin's necklace!
Score!
Hey, I don't think I get what this description means.
Let's go ask one of the shopkeepers.
When you wear this necklace, then you're impervious.
It reflects all of the attack spells directed at you.
And that isn't all.
If you find that any of your cards are under the effects of either the clone or fake cards,
you can restore them with a touch.
Hear that?
If we wear this, we won't have to worry about losing any cards.
Okay, memory helmet?
Witch's love potion, risky dice, king white stag beetle, gold dust girl, and paladin's necklace.
A total of six different specified slot cards.
Piece of cake, huh?
Piece of cake?
Not at all.
This was only possible because of your grueling training.
Huh?
Attention.
Another player has cast contact on you.
Hey, Gon!
It's been a while.
Who are you?
What, you don't remember me?
Well, what about the player who took the Sword of Truth from you in Antakiba?
Remember him?
What do you want?
Up for a trade?
I have number 66, the witch's diet pills, and 27.
That one is the book of VIP passes.
You can talk it over with your friends.
What do you think?
Attention.
Another player has cast contact on you.
Tescara here.
Oh, you again, huh?
Interested in trading your angel's breath for our patch of forest?
It's an SS rank card.
Yeah, no thanks.
As I've already said, I have no desire to deal with you.
What if I throw in a clone?
I thought I made it clear there's no deal here.
You already have 92 different cards.
All that's left are the ones monopolized by the other players.
Isn't that right?
Actually, we have 95.
I'm sure you have some of the items,
and you're waiting for someone else to use gain on them.
In fact, it's entirely possible that Angel's Breath is the last card that you need to obtain.
And I can't think of a single reason we would give that to you and lose the game in the process.
Stop playing, Dome.
I happen to know that you and your people are currently monopolizing both Angel's Breath and Nightjade,
which means the game is not over yet.
Oh.
I wish you boys the best of luck,
but we're never going to let you have these cards.
And if I offer three,
the patch of forest,
spirited away hollow,
and then to top it all off,
there's miniature dragon.
And you only have to give us Nightjade,
not Angel's Breath.
We'd be giving you one SS rank and two S rank,
while you'd only give up an A rank.
That's too good to pass up.
We'll need a little time to discuss it.
To be clear, this is our final offer.
We won't negotiate any further.
Book.
It's gotta be a trap.
It's too good to be true.
Tisgera is awfully cautious.
I doubt he's looking to pick a fight with us.
But that said,
he's not the type to make a losing deal, either.
Which must mean he thinks he can obtain
an Angel's Breath on his own.
What do you think?
I mean, there are 40 types of spell cards.
Does he have all of them?
Maybe, if so.
They're just waiting for us to use gain
on one of our Angel's Breaths.
Could be.
But it took a whole lot of hard work
to monopolize Nightjade.
If one of the cards got destroyed,
one of our Jade jewels would turn back into a card.
Those guys might be able to get their hands
on an SS-rank Angel's Breaths,
but the A-ranked Nightjade
is a lot harder for them to get.
This is a real gamble.
Book.
See ya.
That was surprisingly uneventful.
It was kind of a letdown, actually.
I was so nervous.
But that's seven types in just three days.
We're making real progress.
Okay, let's keep it up.
Are there any other events
for getting restricted slot cards?
Uh, I think there are,
but let me see.
Prizes from the slots?
Well, it is the city of gambling.
You have a 0.01% chance of winning.
That's just one in 10,000.
So it all comes down to luck.
That's pretty risky.
I know.
Hey, Gon, use that dice.
Now, if we get great luck, we can win.
But if you roll worse luck,
something so bad's gonna happen
that it'll cancel out everything good
that's happened to us.
Yeah, but there's only a 1 in 20 chance of that, right?
Yes!
All we gotta do is spin the wheel!
Wow!
Awesome!
First try!
I scored a rainbow diamond!
It's just like I thought.
This little die is the key
to really hitting it big time in this city.
But what if you roll worse luck?
Things could get really scary really quickly.
Don't worry about it.
It's not like it's gonna kill me, right?
Huh?
Oh, no!
A slot machine exploded!
I knew something was wrong.
That guy just hit the jackpot five times in a row.
And he was acting weird.
He kept rolling some funny-looking die.
Whoa!
His face is mushed!
Look!
Okay.
So my vote is that we make the trade.
Yeah, we want all S-ranked cards and above.
And the sooner we obtain them, the better.
True.
But as for A-rank and below...
Roll.
Please spare me!
I'm begging you!
Don't worry.
It's only your third time.
You'll be all right.
But I knew a guy, and he had the worst luck on his first roll, and he died.
Spare me!
If I roll worst luck, that means I'll be hit for every time the other players rolled great luck!
That's not my problem.
Roll it.
Or perhaps you'd rather die now.
Oh, please!
There, see?
It's pretty rare to get worst luck.
Now we'll use the lottery card.
We won number 75, the wild luck Alexandrite.
You got that?
And if you're able to obtain one for us, we'll set you free.
Please.
Oh, please.
Lottery on!
Well?
Number 76.
Ooh, so close.
I guess today's not your lucky day.
Right.
One more.
Roll.
One more time.
Time to see what Motorike's got.
It's time to shine just one more time.
So it didn't happen, huh?
Well, what now, Gen?
Should we make the first move or what?
Like I said, combat is our last resort.
It's still early.
Hold on.
We're trying to stay one step ahead of them, right?
But as soon as we commit, further negotiations will be completely impossible.
What do you have in mind?
We use Tax Collector's Gauntlet combined with Risky Dice.
I understand.
You're saying we use that to steal eight cards from them immediately.
But that'd definitely be dangerous.
If someone rolls worst luck, then they'll probably die.
And this job is too important to leave to them.
Come on.
We've come this far.
Let's clear the game.
Hey, Gen.
What are you doing?
I've told you this before.
When we take a big risk like this one,
we share the danger.
It's Tezgera.
What'll it be?
We're in.
You have yourself a deal.
I'm gonna do it.
Just one more time.
I already said I'm gonna do it.
So I'm gonna do it!
All right.
On to the next city.
Let's go!
Gon and the rest of his team have begun working to beat the game.
The story's climax is drawing near.
I'll walk away.
Let's go!
I'll see you next time.
Coming up, the Great Island Tutorial!